supercross.com 2010-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Supercross.com

Wednesday, 03 June 2009 09:59 

Your privacy is extremely important to Supercross.com. We want you to feel as comfortable as possible visiting our website and using its services. This Privacy Policy and Agreement ("Privacy Policy") tells you what information Supercross.com, Inc. (" _The Company_ ") collects about you and your use of this website. This policy also explains how _The Company_ protects that information and what choices you have about how it is used. We urge you to read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you will understand clearly both our commitment to you and your privacy, and how we may collect and use information. By using the Supercross.com site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

In this privacy policy, we will inform you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected
  * What organization is collecting the information
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What choices are available regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  * What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**1\. What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy applies only to Supercross.com online services, specifically relating to the Free E-News subscription form and the Free Membership enrollment form in which a person may enter their personal information to become an E-News "Subscriber" or a "Member" of the Supercross Community.

Some of the links on this website connect to information hosted by other third-party websites. When you navigate to content that comes from another website (whether through an advertisement, co-brand, service, or content link), be aware that any information you disclose on or through those sites is not subject to this Privacy Policy. Supercross.com does not endorse and is not responsible for the privacy practices of the third party websites to which we link. You should always review the privacy policy for those sites to understand how they treat your personal information.

Within the Site, this Privacy Policy applies only to the information described below. If you enrolled for any Supercross.com Subscription Services, please review the applicable provisions of the separate Subscriber Agreement, as well as the Supercross.com Web Site Use Agreement, to understand how we treat the information you enter when using those services.

**2\. Information Collected by This Website**

Registration and Profile

Personal Information is information that can be used to identify or contact you. You may use this website without submitting personal information. By entering your personal information into a Supercross.com free E-News subscription form or becoming a Member, you consent to the company’s use of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Your personal information will not be shared with any third-party companies or advertisers out of our control. Supercross.com may use the information you enter to contact you by email. Email communications may include information related to specific conditions or topics that interests you, as well as motocross information and news. In most cases, the company will not contact subscribers or members more than once per week.

Cookies

The website may collect anonymous, non-Personal Information about your use of the website through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small computer files that are transferred with your permission to your computer's hard drive. This cookie file recognizes “your computer” (not your personal information) as a repeat visitor and allows the website operator to record how often each computer visits the website and the particular pages viewed by the computer. Every computer is assigned a different cookie by Supercross.com. The information collected by cookies can also help the company dynamically generate content on web pages specifically designed for your interests and also allows the company to statistically monitor how many people are using the site and for what purpose. Cookies also help authenticate users as to not require a password every time the user visits the site from the same PC.

Your browser software can be set to reject all cookies if desired. However, users must at least allow for session-based cookies to use the basic website features. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject cookies in the "Help" section of the toolbar if interested.

Sponsors, partners, advertisers, or other third parties on Supercross.com may also use their own cookies when you click on their advertisement or link to their site or service. Some advertisers use companies other than Supercross.com to serve their ads and these companies ("Ad Servers") may also collect non-Personal Information through the use of cookies on the website. Supercross.com does not control these third parties' use of cookies, or how they manage the non-Personal Information they gather through them. However, we do require Ad Servers to agree that they will not collect any Personal Information from user's visit to a third party advertisement without your consent and to agree they will not link any non-personal cookie information collected by their advertisement to Personal Information they or others collect in other ways or from other websites. You should review the privacy policy of other sites you visit or link to from Supercross.com to understand how these other sites use cookies and how they use the information they collect through the use of cookies on their own sites.

Public Forums

This Privacy Policy can not protect you when you use any public discussion forum, discussion group or web blog such as the community features hosted on Supercross.com. As a service to our users, Supercross.com may feature bulletin boards or online discussions. Any information shared in a bulletin board or online discussion is public information and may be seen or collected by third parties that do not adhere to our Privacy Policy. You should think carefully before disclosing any Personal Information you don't want others to read in any public forum.

**3\. Disclosure of Your Information**

Except as set forth in this Article or as specifically agreed to by you, Supercross.com will not disclose any Personal Information it gathers from you on the Website. The company may release Personal Information to third parties: (1) to comply with valid legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; or (2) in special cases, such as a physical threat to you or others. In the event that we are legally compelled to disclose your Personal Information to a third party, we will notify you unless doing so would violate the law or court order.

Disclosure for Marketing Purposes

Supercross.com may disclose your contact information to its marketing and sales staff for the purpose of contacting you to offer additional services your use of the Website indicates an interest in.

Disclosure in the Context of Linked Websites

Supercross.com will not disclose your Personal Information to the owners and operators of third-party websites linked to the Supercross.com. Please remember that this Privacy Policy no longer applies once you view content hosted by a third party website.

Disclosure of Aggregate Information

Supercross.com may provide to third parties non-Personal Information about its website usage statistics that does not allow you to be identified or contacted and that is combined with the non-Personal Information of other users ("Aggregate Information"). For example, the company might inform third parties regarding the number of users of the Website and the activities they conduct while on the website. Depending on the circumstances, the company may or may not charge third parties for this Aggregate Information. The company also may not limit the third parties use of the Aggregate Information, except that we do require third parties to whom we disclose Aggregate Information to agree that they will not attempt to make this information personally identifiable by combining it with other databases or otherwise.

Third Party Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit [www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and * other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**4\. Your Privacy Choices**

Users will occasionally be presented with the option of receiving informational emails or newsletters from Supercross.com. Users may exercise these options by indicating their email preferences for receiving these communications. In most cases, at the bottom of any email sent from Supercross.com, if you wish to unsubscribe from the list, click on the "UNSUBSCRIBE" link at the bottom of the email to automatically have your information removed from our that newsletter's database of recipients. Your information will be removed immediately upon your completion of the automated unsubscribe process.

**5\. Protecting your Personal Information**

Supercross.com, Inc. takes reasonable technological and physical security measures to protect each user’s Personal Information; however, users must protect their own passwords and log-in information themselves. The Company cannot protect a user’s Personal Information from a third-party who has obtained their log-in and password credentials legally or illegally. User's are cautioned to take great care to protect their own passwords. Some recommended strategies to help protect passwords are as follows:

  * Always select a password that is a mixture of at least 7 letters and numbers that cannot be easily associated with your known personal information.
  * Never enter your password in the presence of another person who could watch you type it.
  * Never use the same password on different websites that are insecure or possibly run by companies which do not protect your Personal Information.

**6\. Updating Your Personal Information and Contacting Supercross.com**

You can always contact us in order to (1) delete your Personal Information or (2) update the Personal Information that you have provided to us by emailing us at [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy58036%20=%20'support'%20+%20'@';%20addy58036%20=%20addy58036%20+%20'Supercross'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy58036%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy58036%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[support@Supercross.com](mailto:support@Supercross.com) . Such changes will not have any effect on other information that Supercross.com maintains. You may not delete your Personal Information if you wish to continue access to the Website and/or our Supercross.com members-only services.

It is not technologically reasonable to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to Supercross.com from our computers servers. The need to back-up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your Personal Information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for the company to locate. Nevertheless, upon receiving your request, all Personal Information stored in the live active databases we host will be removed.

Privacy as it applies to the Internet is a dynamic, rapidly developing area. In the future, the company may make significant changes to its privacy policy affecting the use of the Personal Information it collects. The company will notify users by email of any significant material changes to its privacy policy and obtain your "opt-in" consent to any significant new uses of your Personal Information, if it was collected from you prior to a significant change in this policy. The company may also make non-significant changes to our Privacy Policy that generally will not affect the use of your Personal Information. You should also check this posted Privacy Policy for any future changes. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or any revised policy, please exit the site immediately and terminate your membership in Supercross.com.

---|---|---
